### Contact

7828837940 (Mobile) vatsalpandey2011.vp@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/vatsal-pandey-174b8618b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Photography

C++

Video Editing

### Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

English (Limited Working)

### Certifications

Python for Data Science and Al Introduction to Artificial Intelligence Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) Industry 4.0

### Honors-Awards

IBM Badge for 'Python for Data Science And Al'

# Vatsal Pandey

Student at National Institute of Technology Raipur Raipur

## Summary

Experienced Executive with a demonstrated history of working in the non profit organization Management industry. Fairly proficient in Python Programming Language, C++, C, Adobe Tools, MS Office Tools with Bachelor of Technology focused in Metallurgical Engineering from National institute Of Technology, Raipur.

## Experience

Click Club, NIT Raipur 2 years 1 month

Core Coordinator April 2020 - Present (5 months) Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

#### Executive

August 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 8 months)

Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

METSO, NIT Raipur

1 year 2 months

Core Coordinator April 2020 - Present (5 months)

Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

Joint Secretary July 2019 - March 2020 (9 months)

Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

Technocracy - The Technical Committee, NIT Raipur Executive

April 2019 - April 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

## Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Metallurgical Engineering · (2018 - 2022)

Kendriya Vidyalaya, Raigarh · (2016 - 2018)